<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ten Thousand Worlds on Game Manglement</title>
    <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/tags/ten-thousand-worlds/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Ten Thousand Worlds on Game Manglement</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/tags/ten-thousand-worlds/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ten Thousand Worlds: Dynasts</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/dynast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/dynast/</guid>
      <description>Soon after the Influx, the Captains of the great colony ships and the first stations established themselves as absolute rulers of their domains. Power was passed down through their family lines and those of their subordinates, and over the centuries they built great trading empires, fleets and Worlds.
Hundreds of families formed the Great and Lesser Houses of these Dynasties, with their reach and influence appearing supreme. They felt they had the right and privilege to do anything, to anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Ten Thousand Worlds: Technadepts</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/technadept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/technadept/</guid>
      <description>Cybernetics in the 10K are pretty common, usually used to replace damaged or missing limbs or other organs. Technadepts, however, take the use of cybernetics and implanted technologies to the next level. Technadept implants are always far more advanced than anything freely available, sometimes even alien in origin, and they have used this to build an air of mysticism around what they are capable of, referring to the effects they create as “spells” or “incantations”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysteries, Wonders and Dangers of The Ten Thousand Worlds: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/wonders_part_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/wonders_part_1/</guid>
      <description>There are many mysteries, wonders and dangers in the Ten Thousand Worlds, some of them are worth a lot of money to those brave enough to investigate them. Most of them will kill you stone dead.
Welcome to the Ten Thousand Worlds.
The Testament of Cycles The Testament of Cycles is, looking at at it simplistically, a book - but quite unlike any other book in existence. Firstly, it is not a physical object (although physical copies of parts of it have been made).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to The Ten Thousand Worlds</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/introduction/</guid>
      <description>The Ten Thousand Worlds is a (work-in-progress) futuristic science fantasy setting. If you want to get a feel for life in the 10K, think Firefly, a bit of Guardians of the Galaxy, some Doctor Who and Farscape and a fair bit of The Expanse.
Introduction Somewhere, in some star system light years away and a long time ago, Earth died.
The Human Race, knowing the end was coming, migrated en masse to a new home.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>