<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Downcrawl on Game Manglement</title>
    <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/tags/downcrawl/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Downcrawl on Game Manglement</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/tags/downcrawl/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Downcrawl: Session Three</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_three/</guid>
      <description>Standing in the doorway of the Alchemist&#39;s Tower, the blood drained from Sherman&#39;s face as he looked out onto streets swarming with green-eyed undead shambling and stumbling toward them.
&amp;ldquo;How many?&amp;quot;, said Eirik, limbering up his massive shoulders and arms ready for the coming fight.
&amp;ldquo;Err&amp;hellip; all of &amp;lsquo;em, I think&amp;rdquo;, said Sherman. Eirik&#39;s face went blank with thought.
&amp;ldquo;Door?&amp;quot;, asked Sherman. &amp;ldquo;Door&amp;rdquo;, Eirik nodded, and they started looking around for something to bar the door with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downcrawl: Session Two</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_two/</guid>
      <description>When last we saw our heroes, they had just been hired by local &amp;ldquo;businessman&amp;rdquo; and rather colorfully-dressed elf, Gwindore, to head for the catacombs far above Bone Falls and search for another party of adventurers sent in some weeks ago and who have not reappeared since. Gwindore was willing to pay them 10 keys each with another 5 keys per adventurer found alive. Cuthmar had still not appeared after the party lost him in the tunnels outside Bone Falls days ago, and now Celiophane had also gone missing, but intent on making a fast fortune, Sherman and Eirik set on their way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downcrawl: Session One</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_one/</guid>
      <description>When we first met our heroes, they were already well on the way to making a name for themselves. Sherman, Cuthmar, Eirik and Celiophane had taken on the task of rescuing a local merchant’s daughter from a band of marauding goblins, tracked the goblins to their cave-lair and fought their way to the goblin shaman who was about to make a blood sacrifice of the young girl. They figured they’d won, but with his dying breath the shaman uttered a dire curse.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>