<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Manglement</title>
    <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Game Manglement</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Empires for Roleplaying: The Hyperion Cantos</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/articles/empires_hyperion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/articles/empires_hyperion/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to science-fiction roleplaying games, Traveller is granddaddy of them all, and it has it&#39;s own setting (the Third Imperium) that&#39;s been around from day one. Outside role-playing (but supported by several different games over the years) you have universes such as Star Wars, Star Trek and, more recently, The Expanse. But what other &amp;ldquo;universes&amp;rdquo; are there out there for adventuring, what kinds of stories might they inspire, and what RPG systems suit their particular style of story telling.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Building Compendia for Foundry VTT</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/articles/vtt_compendia_building/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/articles/vtt_compendia_building/</guid>
      <description>Creating A Compendium From the official Knowledge Base and the community web site, there are two explanations given on how to create a compendium for Foundry VTT, others are often discussed on the Discord server. The first, and most obvious, is to create it manually within a game world, but this has several limitations: it&#39;s slow and time consuming to create and edit once created, and (without some jiggery-pokery) the compendium is bound to that particular world and not easily re-used across several game worlds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysteries, Wonders and Dangers of The Ten Thousand Worlds: Part 2</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/wonders_part_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 May 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/wonders_part_2/</guid>
      <description>There are many mysteries, wonders and dangers in the Ten Thousand Worlds, some of them are worth a lot of money to those brave enough to investigate them. Most of them will kill you stone dead.
Welcome to the Ten Thousand Worlds.
The Vylk Enclave   The Vylk are the only (known) alien race in the Ten Thousand Worlds, and the Vylk Enclave is a marvel of megastructure engineering. By far the largest of the Worlds, and likely one of the oldest, it sits on the outer edge of the system far above the plane of the ecliptic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wolves of God: Adventures in Dark Ages England</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/posts/wolves_of_god_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Apr 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/posts/wolves_of_god_review/</guid>
      <description>It is 710 AD. It is an age of iron and ruin, a wolf-season amid the ashes of Roman Britain. The spears of the English tribes are raised against their rivals, and the Wealh of the western hills remember bitterly what was taken from them. The shattered caesters of past Roman glory litter the land, each one laden with forgotten troves hidden by desperate men of the last days. Sorcerous Arxes once sealed against a Roman rescue that never came are now cracking open, the changed refugees within now seeking vengeance for a ruin of centuries past.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downcrawl: Session Four</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_four/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Mar 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_four/</guid>
      <description>Swept away by the huge wave, Eirik and Sherman struggled to stay afloat for what seemed like hours, but was probably only a few minutes. Their feet first brushed, then settled on solid ground and, as the water drained away, they could just make out in the dim Fuzz light, that they had come to rest on a smooth stone floor. Beyond more than a dozen feet or so, what little light there was faded into a grey nothingness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downcrawl: Session Three</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_three/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_three/</guid>
      <description>Standing in the doorway of the Alchemist&#39;s Tower, the blood drained from Sherman&#39;s face as he looked out onto streets swarming with green-eyed undead shambling and stumbling toward them.
&amp;ldquo;How many?&amp;quot;, said Eirik, limbering up his massive shoulders and arms ready for the coming fight.
&amp;ldquo;Err&amp;hellip; all of &amp;lsquo;em, I think&amp;rdquo;, said Sherman. Eirik&#39;s face went blank with thought.
&amp;ldquo;Door?&amp;quot;, asked Sherman. &amp;ldquo;Door&amp;rdquo;, Eirik nodded, and they started looking around for something to bar the door with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten Thousand Worlds: Adepts</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/adept/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/adept/</guid>
      <description>Cybernetics in the Worlds are pretty common, used to replace damaged or missing limbs or other organs. Adepts, however, take the use of cybernetics and implanted technologies to the next level. Their implants are always far more advanced than anything freely available, sometimes even alien in origin, and they have used this to build an air of mysticism around what they are capable of, referring to the effects they create as “hexes” or “incantations”.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ten Thousand Worlds: Dynasts</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/dynast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/dynast/</guid>
      <description>Soon after the Influx, the Captains of the great colony ships and the first stations established themselves as absolute rulers of their domains. Power was passed down through their family lines and those of their subordinates, and over the centuries they built great trading empires, fleets and Worlds.
Hundreds of families formed the Great and Lesser Houses of these Dynasties, with their reach and influence appearing supreme. They felt they had the right and privilege to do anything, to anyone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downcrawl: Session Two</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_two/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_two/</guid>
      <description>When last we saw our heroes, they had just been hired by local &amp;ldquo;businessman&amp;rdquo; and rather colorfully-dressed elf, Gwindore, to head for the catacombs far above Bone Falls and search for another party of adventurers sent in some weeks ago and who have not reappeared since. Gwindore was willing to pay them 10 keys each with another 5 keys per adventurer found alive. Cuthmar had still not appeared after the party lost him in the tunnels outside Bone Falls days ago, and now Celiophane had also gone missing, but intent on making a fast fortune, Sherman and Eirik set on their way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Chivalry &amp; Sorcery - 5th Edition, First Read</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/posts/cns_5th_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/posts/cns_5th_review/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, we&#39;ve seen a lot of early RPGs, such as Traveller and Runequest, resurrected in new editions with cleaner rules and more modern presentations which, for the most part, have retained the original feel of the game. Chivalry &amp;amp; Sorcery has seen several editions over the years, the last almost 20 years ago in 2000 (not counting the 2011 &amp;ldquo;Essence&amp;rdquo; release which was only 44 pages). Now, following a successful Kickstarter, a new 5th Edition has returned at a whopping 602 pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downcrawl: Session One</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_one/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/downcrawl/session_one/</guid>
      <description>When we first met our heroes, they were already well on the way to making a name for themselves. Sherman, Cuthmar, Eirik and Celiophane had taken on the task of rescuing a local merchant’s daughter from a band of marauding goblins, tracked the goblins to their cave-lair and fought their way to the goblin shaman who was about to make a blood sacrifice of the young girl. They figured they’d won, but with his dying breath the shaman uttered a dire curse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Trek Adventures: Search and Rescue</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/articles/sta_sar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/articles/sta_sar/</guid>
      <description>The Star Trek Adventures: Command Division sourcebook introduced stats for new ships from Star Trek canon, many of which have either never been seen or seen only rarely on-screen. Among them is the Norway Class, which was designed by the Advanced Starship Design Bureau for rapid emergency response. So, what&#39;s it like being on the crew of one of these ships, what adventures can you have and how do you handle them?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mysteries, Wonders and Dangers of The Ten Thousand Worlds: Part 1</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/wonders_part_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/wonders_part_1/</guid>
      <description>There are many mysteries, wonders and dangers in the Ten Thousand Worlds, some of them are worth a lot of money to those brave enough to investigate them. Most of them will kill you stone dead.
Welcome to the Ten Thousand Worlds.
The Testament of Cycles The Testament of Cycles is, looking at at it simplistically, a book - but quite unlike any other book in existence. Firstly, it is not a physical object (although physical copies of parts of it have been made).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to The Ten Thousand Worlds</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/introduction/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/campaigns/ten_thousand_worlds/introduction/</guid>
      <description>The Ten Thousand Worlds is a (work-in-progress) futuristic science fantasy setting. If you want to get a feel for life in the Worlds, think Firefly, a bit of Guardians of the Galaxy, some Doctor Who and Farscape and a fair bit of The Expanse.
Introduction Somewhere, in a star system light years away and a long time ago, Earth died.
The Human Race, knowing the end was coming, migrated en masse to a new home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Star Trek Adventures: Fighters</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/articles/sta_fighters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/articles/sta_fighters/</guid>
      <description>The Command Division sourcebook for Star Trek Adventures includes, almost hidden away in the Federation Small Craft chapter, the details of the Federation Attack Fighter, also called the Zabathu1 class (after an Andorian riding animal). This is really the first reference in the rules made to any sort of fighter class ship and, to be sure, such craft are rarely seen in Star Trek itself. Most ship battles on screen are between two or more capital ships which make up the vast majority of any faction’s fleet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brass: Kickstarter Edition, Review</title>
      <link>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/posts/brass_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pumbers.github.io/game-manglement/posts/brass_review/</guid>
      <description>Brass is a board game set in Lancashire, England during the Industrial Revolution, developed by Martin Wallace and originally released in 2007. The object is to use cards and cash to build mines, cotton factories, ports, canals and rail links, and establish trade routes, all of which will be used to victory score points. This review covers the newly-released Lancashire and Birmingham editions from the 2017 Kickstarter campaign by Roxley Games.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>